我来了  老板
Here you go, Boss.
告诉我你最喜欢哪一个  可以吗
Let me know which one you like best, all right?
等我们决定了  会告诉你的
Well, when we decide, we will let you know.
但是首先  我想先来谈谈洗碗机的事儿
But first, I wanted to talk about the, uh -- the dishwasher.
我说了要放在左边
Uh, I wanted it over here on the left,
但不知为何  你把它放在右边了
but now, for some reason, it's on the right.
我要你按我要求的把洗碗机放在左边
I would like it on the left like I asked.
听懂我的主张了吗
Asserted?
不不不  眼睛  眼睛看这里  好吗
No, no, no, no. Eyes -- Eyes over here, okay?
这事儿我说了算
This -- This is my thing.
给你看个东西
Well, let me show you something.
-好  -你看看水池下面
- Yeah. ?- All right, look under the sink.
没问题
Will do.
蹲下去  到最下面
Go down. All the way.
好了  现在钻到里头去
Okay, now, get in there.
抬头看  你看到你左边的管子了吗
Look up. Do you see that post on your left?
等等  好了
Wait. Ho-- Okay.